https://www.militarywatchexchange.com/privacy-policy

Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
Tritium Military Compass
Join our mailing list today and be the first to hear all about our latest updates, offers and promotions!
Privacy Policy
2020 N.E. 163 Street - Suite 399North Miami Beach, Florida 33162 Toll Free: 866.586.4669 Outside US: 305.948.0103PRIVACY POLICYInformation Collection and UseMilitarywatchexchange.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Militarywatchexchange.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.Order We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.Log FilesWe use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.LinksThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Militarywatchexchange.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.SecurityThis website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [https://ssl.comodo.com/].While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can contact us. Choice/Opt-outOur users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, [Some sites are able to offer opt-out mechanisms on member information pages and also supply a telephone or postal option as a way to opt-out.]Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our privacy page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. All information gathered by Militarywatchexchange.com during your order is kept strictly confidential and will not be distributed. The information will be used only to make sure that your order gets delivered to you in the timeliest manner.
Our Company
MilitaryWatchexchange.com
2020 N.E. 163rd St Suite 300
North Miami Beach, FL 33162
Questions, Orders, Inquiries
Toll Free: 866.586.4669
International: 305.948.0103
UK: 020.8133.9312
Monday - Friday 9am-5pm Est.
Copyright © 2020 Military Watch Exchange. All rights reserved.
Powered by BigCommerce
